{"cards":[{"mId":"15024a6c-ea3e-433e-8ef2-7f346a4ba916","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to end a romantic relationship","mBack":"to break up"},{"mId":"1a268ef0-ea4b-404f-ad7b-0827e9a08b96","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to become less close to someone","mBack":"to drift apart"},{"mId":"890d4a52-879d-44d7-8bc8-e4c615f3195a","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to fall in love","mBack":"to fall for"},{"mId":"c394bebd-76d7-42a0-8a93-d505c21bbeed","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to start to love someone a lot","mBack":"to fall head over heels in love"},{"mId":"69cafd25-7caa-4bec-a60f-15be8e16b2cd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to have a disagreement and stop being friends","mBack":"to fall out with"},{"mId":"b44720d9-5e57-496f-97db-b033fbcd120f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to like someone\u0027s company very much indeed","mBack":"to get on like a house on fire"},{"mId":"733d1fc6-a45b-4272-bc39-6419cb429cdd","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to understand someone and enjoy similar interests","mBack":"to get on well with"},{"mId":"4f753025-528e-4742-b591-5f6169c200a8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to begin to know someone","mBack":"to get to know"},{"mId":"78ecd70a-9b69-4f58-bfd9-ecf9700fd933","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to have known someone for a long time","mBack":"to go back years"},{"mId":"b5919f0f-146a-4e9b-b271-052b7c61e37f","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to share similar interests","mBack":"to have a lot in common"},{"mId":"ea89c0dc-edf9-4c16-b268-734f383673b9","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to have good and bad times","mBack":"to have ups and downs"},{"mId":"028126c0-a848-4947-9d0a-f37592bf7e02","mCardType":"text","mFront":"a good, positive relationship","mBack":"a healthy relationship"},{"mId":"fed5620a-d803-44be-8a29-d557c1a1609e","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to quickly become good friends with","mBack":"to hit it off"},{"mId":"b6431089-18fb-4ecd-a13b-a89d33ceb1d8","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to be romantically involved with someone","mBack":"to be in a relationship"},{"mId":"af790493-ae35-4f5c-bb92-750452a9e3bf","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to not be romantically involved","mBack":"to be just good friends"},{"mId":"4d948c9c-75d3-4962-86e7-b61be0083b59","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to keep in contact with","mBack":"to keep in touch with"},{"mId":"297e647a-8fab-496e-a15b-192706ccf5b3","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to not see or hear from someone any longer","mBack":"to lose touch with"},{"mId":"e9ca5216-61cc-474f-ade0-ab59cdf047a0","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to fall in love immediately you meet someone","mBack":"ove at first sight"},{"mId":"f8cb1a57-9073-4536-af22-8e6165f41376","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to ask someone to marry you","mBack":"to pop the question"},{"mId":"50f8a549-04a4-48c1-97a8-e1f5ef044c62","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to agree on a subject","mBack":"to see eye to eye"},{"mId":"f2a57708-e9d8-4298-bf47-92045cf20cfc","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to give up the single life and start a family","mBack":"to settle down"},{"mId":"535c810c-359e-4baa-bcd6-deb7561115be","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to begin a friendship","mBack":"to strike up a relationship"},{"mId":"34f2b01b-e422-46e6-9c64-8ecc907fd13d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to get married","mBack":"to tie the knot"},{"mId":"b0d56a79-cd07-4cf1-8892-b85de5fd440d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to be similar to","mBack":"to be well matched"},{"mId":"f2a7a380-7b33-47b8-a1bd-ddc46637511d","mCardType":"text","mFront":"to try to maintain a positive relationship with someone","mBack":"to work at a relationship"}]}